Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980
    - Opulent Past -- Correspondence, 1991 July-1992 August (Box II:12, Folder 33)
    - Opulent Past -- Italian Trade Commission, 1992 June-July (Box II:12, Folder 34)
    - Opulent Past -- Contract, 1992 April (Box II:12, Folder 35)
    - Opulent Past -- Invitation Labels, Circa 1992 (Box II:12, Folder 36)
    - Opulent Past -- Invoices, 1990 November-1992 June (Box II:12, Folder 37)
    - Opulent Past -- Shipping, 1992 April-1993 May (Box II:12, Folder 38)
    - Opulent Past -- Dispersal, 1992 June-August (Box II:12, Folder 39)
    - John Kohring (Small Gallery), 1992 May-August (Box II:12, Folder 40)
    - John Kohring (Small Gallery), 1992 May (Box II:12, Folder 41)
    - Michael Richards (Windows), 1992 June-August (Box II:12, Folder 42)
    - Camera As Weapon -- Correspondence, 1989 June-1992 November (Box II:12, Folder 43)
    - Camera As Weapon -- Contract, 1990 January-August (Box II:12, Folder 44)
    - Adrian Piper -- Decide Who You Are, 1992 July-November (Box II:12, Folder 45)
    - Adrian Piper -- Colloquium, 1991 August-1992 October (Box II:12, Folder 46)
    - Adrian Piper -- Loans, 1992 September (Box II:12, Folder 47)
    - Jeff Gates (Windows), 1989 August-1993 February (Box II:12, Folder 48)
    - Australian AIDS Posters, 1992 August-1993 August (Box II:12, Folder 49)
    - Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), 1992 October-1993 January (Box II:12, Folder 50)
    - Gotscho -- Correspondence and Shipping, 1992 March-December (Box II:12, Folder 51)
    - Gotscho -- Loans and Condition, 1992 October-1993 January (Box II:12, Folder 52)
    - Gotscho -- Finance/Contract, Undated (Box II:12, Folder 53)
    - Joshua Neustein -- Correspondence and Shipping, 1991 April-1993 March (Box II:12, Folder 54)
    - Joshua Neustein -- Lenders and Contracts, 1991 December-1993 May (Box II:12, Folder 55)
    - Jane Gifford -- Correspondence and Shipping, 1992 March-1993 April (Box II:12, Folder 56)
    - Jane Gifford -- Loans, 1993 August (Box II:12, Folder 57)
    - Alan Michelson (Windows), 1993 January-May (Box II:12, Folder 58)
    - NetherArt -- Finance/Contract, 1993 March (Box II:12, Folder 59)
    - Other Borders -- Registration, 1993 April-July (Box II:12, Folder 60)
    - Other Borders -- Finance/Contract, 1992 April-1993 May (Box II:12, Folder 61)
    - Matthew Benedict (Windows), 1993 June-September (Box II:12, Folder 62)
    - George Platt Lybes -- Finance/Contract, 1992 March-1993 September (Box II:12, Folder 63)
    - George Platt Lynes -- Finance/Contract, 1994 July 22 (Box II:12, Folder 64)
    - George Platt Lynes -- Registration, 1992 July-1994 November (Box II:12, Folder 65)
    - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993 September-October (Box II:12, Folder 66)
    - Jim Hodges (Windows), 1993 September-November (Box II:12, Folder 67)
    - Anyone in New York -- Finance/Contract, 1993 August-1994 April (Box II:12, Folder 68)
    - Brief Encounters -- Registration, 1993 October-1994 January (Box II:12, Folder 69)
    - Lydia Schouten (Windows), 1993 September-1994 January (Box II:12, Folder 70)
    - Visual Aids (Small Gallery), 1994 January-March (Box II:12, Folder 71)
    - Art About Aids -- Finance/Contract, 1991 January-1992 August (Box II:12, Folder 72)
    - Art About Aids -- Registration, 1993 January-1994 June (Box II:12, Folder 73)
    - Joseph Stashkevetch, 1994 March (Box II:12, Folder 74)
    - Todd Watts -- Finance/Contract, 1992 March-1993 February (Box II:12, Folder 75)
    - Todd Watts -- Registration, 1994 January-July (Box II:12, Folder 76)
    - Three Women in Black (Windows), 1994 March-June (Box II:12, Folder 77)
    - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Registration, 1994 April-October (Box II:12, Folder 78)
    - Rob Wynne (Windows), 1994 August (Box II:13, Folder 1)
    - Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), 1994 June-August (Box II:13, Folder 2)
    - Willie Doherty -- Finance/Contract, 1993 September-1994 August (Box II:13, Folder 3)
    - Willie Doherty -- Registration, 1994 August-November (Box II:13, Folder 4)
    - John Defazio (Small Gallery), 1994 August (Box II:13, Folder 5)
    - Rene Santos -- Finance/Contract, 1994 January-October (Box II:13, Folder 6)
    - Rene Santos -- Registration (Lenders), 1994 September-1995 September (Box II:13, Folder 7)
    - Rene Santos -- Registration (Shipping), 1994 September-1995 July (Box II:13, Folder 8)
    - Scot Cohen (Windows), 1994 November-1995 January (Box II:13, Folder 9)
    - Narelle Jubelin -- Registration, 1995 January-March (Box II:13, Folder 10)
    - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1995 January-March (Box II:13, Folder 11)
    - Ann Mandelbaum -- Registration, 1995 March-May (Box II:13, Folder 12)
    - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1995 March-May (Box II:13, Folder 13)
    - Ed McGowan (Windows), 1995 March (Box II:13, Folder 14)
    - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Registration, 1995 May (Box II:13, Folder 15)
    - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995 August (Box II:13, Folder 16)
    - Traditions/Tensions -- Agreements and Loans, 1996 (Box II:13, Folder 17)
  - Subseries E: Annual Reports, 1966-1974
    This subseries contains two folders of annual reports generated by the New York University Art Collection, recording its yearly acquisitions and activities.
    - Annual Reports, 1966-1972 (Box II:14, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-1974 (Box II:14, Folder 2)
- Series III: Oversize, 1963-2011
  This series contains oversized objects that are too large to fit into Series I, II, and IV.
  - Morse Research, Undated (Box III:1, File 1)
  - Bay Area Painting, 1957 (Box III:1, File 2)
  - Exhibition: Glassboro State College, 1969 (Box III:1, File 3)
  - Apollo - The Magazine of the Arts, 1972 September (Box III:1, File 4)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Victoria and Albert Museum, 1972 December 14-1973 January 28 (Box III:1, File 5)
  - D. Hare/ F. Kiesler Publicity/ Biographical Information, 1976 May (Box III:1, File 6)
  - Panoramic Photography - Hand List of the Exhibit, 1977 September 23-November 2 (Box III:1, File 7)
  - Elgort, Arthur, Circa 1980-1985 (Box III:1, File 8)
  - Two Installations -- Correspondence, 1982 (Box III:1, File 9)
  - Portrait Photography PR, 1982 August (Box III:1, File 10)
  - Kahlo/Modotti - Bob's File, Circa 1982-1983 (Box III:1, File 11)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe Review, Circa 1982-1983 (Box III:1, File 12)
  - Hockney, David, 1982-1983 (Box III:1, File 13)
  - Louise Dahl-Wolfe RRL File, 1983 (Box III:1, File 14)
  - Picasso - The New York Times Magazine, 1984 February 26 (Box III:1, File 15)
  - Precious -- Catalogue and Notes, Circa 1984-1985 (Box III:2, File 1)
  - Contemporary Indian Art -- Catalogue Drafts, 1985 November (Box III:2, File 2)
  - Rosalyn Drexler, 1984 July-November (Box III:2, File 3)
  - Precious -- Photos and Transparencies, Circa 1984-1985 (Box III:2, File 4)
  - Precious -- Bibliograpy, Undated (Box III:2, File 5)
  - Unidentified Labels, Circa 1984-1987 (Box III:2, File 6)
  - Jaar/Sheehan -- Installation Pieces, 1987 June 7 (Box III:2, File 7)
  - Harrisons -- Newsletter Conversation, 1987 (Box III:2, File 8)
  - Andy Warhol -- Reviews, 1989 February-August (Box III:3, File 1)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Grey Reviews and Lournay Ads, 1988 February-July (Box III:3, File 2)
  - Black Mountain College -- Proofs, Undated (Box III:3, File 3)
  - Cecil Beaton -- London Information Folder, Undated (Box III:3, File 4)
  - Andy Warhole -- Press (Grey Gallery), 1989 September-October (Box III:3, File 5)
  - Black Mountain College -- Reviews, 1987 December (Box III:3, File 6)
  - Black Mountain -- Exhibition List and Bibliography, Circa 1987 (Box III:3, File 7)
  - Black Mountain College -- Checklist for Exhibition, 1987 (Box III:3, File 8)
  - Andy Warhole -- Press (Lingotto), 1990 (Box III:4, File 1)
  - Andy Warhole -- Catalog Draft, Circa 1988-1990 (Box III:4, File 2)
  - Andy Warhole -- Text Panel and Labels, Circa 1988-1990 (Box III:4, File 3)
  - Andy Warhol -- Foundation Cartier, 1990 (Box III:4, File 4)
  - Rosalind Solomon, Circa 1987-1988 (Box III:4, File 5)
  - Rosalind Solomon, 1986-1988 (Box III:4, File 6)
  - Show and Tell -- Labels, Circa 1986-1988 (Box III:4, File 7)
  - Show and Tell -- Layout/Design, Undated (Box III:4, File 8)
  - Out of Eastern Europe, 1986 (Box III:4, File 9)
  - Hujar -- Images (2 of 2), 1976-1987 (Box III:5, File 1)
  - Hujar -- Images (1 of 2), 1976-1987 (Box III:5, File 2)
  - Hujar -- Press, 1990 October (Box III:5, File 3)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Notes, Undated (Box III:5, File 4)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Printed Materials and Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box III:5, File 5)
  - Etruscan Exhibition, 1988-1990 (Box III:5, File 6)
  - Zuka - The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery), 1989 (Box III:5, File 7)
  - Excommunication, 1989 March 3-9 (Box III:5, File 8)
  - Anyone in New York -- Exhibition (Catalog), 1993 (Box III:6, Folder 1)
  - Anyone in New York -- Public Relations, 1993 December-1994 August (Box III:6, Folder 2)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibition Materials, Circa 1991-1992 (Box III:6, Folder 3)
  - Brazilian Exhibition -- Regina Silveira and Nelson Leirner, Circa 1990-1991 (Box III:6, Folder 4)
  - Arne Svenson (Windows), Circa 1991-1992 (Box III:6, Folder 5)
  - Three Women in Black (Windows), Circa 1993-1994 (Box III:6, Folder 6)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994 (Box III:6, Folder 7)
  - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1995 (Box III:6, Folder 8)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Exhibition, Circa 1994-1995 (Box III:6, Folder 9)
  - Rene Santos -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994 (Box III:6, Folder 10)
  - Willie Doherty -- Exhibition, 1994 (Box III:6, Folder 11)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995 (Box III:6, Folder 12)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), Undated (Box III:6, Folder 13)
  - Adrian Piper -- Decide Who You Are, Circa 1991-1992 (Box III:6, Folder 14)
  - Camera As Weapon, Circa 1992 (Box III:6, Folder 15)
  - Opulent Past -- Installation, Circa 1992 (Box III:6, Folder 16)
  - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993 November 1 (Box III:7, Folder 1)
  - Space Photography -- Image Requests (JPL), 1981 (Box III:7, Folder 2)
  - Umbria Press, 1988-1989 (Box III:7, Folder 3)
  - Life -- Bookings (No Response or Rejections), Circa 1979 (Box III:7, Folder 4)
  - NetherArt -- Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box III:7, Folder 5)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature, 1981 (Box III:7, Folder 6)
  - Tanya Grosman -- Dinner, Circa 1981 (Box III:7, Folder 7)
  - American Symbolist -- Pivar Notes, Circa 1978-1979 (Box III:7, Folder 8)
  - Space Photography -- Life Magazine, 1981 June (Box III:7, Folder 9)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Poster, Circa 1980-1982 (Box III:7, Folder 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz, Circa 1980-1981 (Box III:7, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Press, 1988-1989 (Box III:7, Folder 12)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, 1984 May (Box III:8, Folder 1)
  - Show and Tell, Circa 1988 (Box III:8, Folder 2)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalog, Circa 1988-1990 (Box III:8, Folder 3)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Press, 1996 (Box III:8, Folder 4)
  - NetherArt, 1993 (Box III:8, Folder 5)
  - Space Photography -- Catalog, Circa 1980-1981 (Box III:8, Folder 6)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog (John Myers Essay), 1981 (Box III:8, Folder 7)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Brochure, 1981 (Box III:8, Folder 8)
  - Rosalind Solomon: Portraits in the Time of Aids -- Catalog, 1987-1988 (Box III:8, Folder 9)
  - Touching North -- Book, 1989 (Box III:8, Folder 10)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Bennington College, Undated (Box III:8, Folder 11)
  - Burra and Nash -- Works Requested, Undated (Box III:8, Folder 12)
  - Documentation re items from "Triangle Fire Exhibition offered to NYU Archives", 2011 (Box III:8, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Publications, 1960-2020
  This series contains printed catalogs and other publications used by the gallery.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Undated Catalogs (Box IV:1, Folder 1)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1960-1975 (Box IV:1, Folder 2)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1967-1973 (Box IV:1, Folder 3)
  - "Contemporary South West Asian-North African Graphics", 1969 (Box IV:1, Folder 4)
  - Abby Weed Grey, 1970-1976 (Box IV:1, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs, 1976-1978 (Box IV:1, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs, 1976-1979 (Box IV:1, Folder 7)
  - "American Painting: The Eighties", 1979 (Box IV:1, Folder 8)
  - "Life: The First Decade", 1979 (Box IV:1, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs, 1980 (Box IV:1, Folder 10)
  - "Italian Drawings 1780-1890" (1981), 1980 (Box IV:1, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs, 1980-1981 (Box IV:1, Folder 12)
  - "Judson Dance Theater: 1962-1966" (1982), 1981 (Box IV:1, Folder 13)
  - "Tracking the Marvelous", 1981 (Box IV:1, Folder 24)
  - Catalogs, 1981-1982 (Box IV:1, Folder 14)
  - Catalogs, 1982 (Box IV:1, Folder 15)
  - Abby Weed Grey Autobiography, 1983 (Box IV:1, Folder 16)
  - Catalogs, 1983 (Box IV:1, Folder 17)
  - Catalogs, 1984 (Box IV:1, Folder 18)
  - Catalogs, 1985 (Box IV:1, Folder 19)
  - Catalogs, 1986 (Box IV:1, Folder 20)
  - "Modern Redux", 1986 (Box IV:1, Folder 21)
  - Catalogs, 1987-1988 (Box IV:1, Folder 22)
  - "Cecil Beaton", 1988 (Box IV:1, Folder 23)
  - Catalogs, 1990-1991 (Box IV:2, Folder 1)
  - "Yasuzo Nojima and Contemporaries", 1991 (Box IV:2, Folder 2)
  - "Out of the Opulent Past", 1992 (Box IV:2, Folder 3)
  - Umbria, 1991 (Box IV:2, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs, 1992 (Box IV:2, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue, 1992-1993 (Box IV:2, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs, 1994-1995 (Box IV:2, Folder 7)
  - Catalogs, 1995 (Box IV:2, Folder 8)
  - "Traditions/Tensions: Contemporary Art in Asia", 1996 (Box IV:2, Folder 9)
  - "Philip Morris Art Award", 1996 (Box IV:2, Folder 10)
  - Catalogs and Publications, 1997 (Box IV:2, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs, 1997-1998 (Box IV:2, Folder 12)
  - "Rudy Burckhardt", 1998 (Box IV:2, Folder 13)
  - "Police Pictures: Photographs As Evidence", 1998 (Box IV:2, Folder 14)
  - "Philip Morris Award", 1998 (Box IV:2, Folder 15)
  - "Inverted Odysseys", 1999 (Box IV:2, Folder 16)
  - "When Time Began to Rant and Rage", 1999 (Box IV:2, Folder 17)
  - "Karel Teige/1900-1951" (2001), 1999 (Box IV:2, Folder 18)
  - "Face to Face", 2000 (Box IV:3, Folder 1)
  - "Images from Sheer Realities: Clothing and Power in Nineteenth Century Philippines", 2000 (Box IV:3, Folder 2)
  - "Ben Shah's New York", 2000 (Box IV:3, Folder 3)
  - "Shifting Tides: Cuban Photography After the Revolution", 2001 (Box IV:3, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs and Publications, 2001-2002 (Box IV:3, Folder 5)
  - "Zeitgenossische Fotokunst Aus Der Schweiz", 2002 (Box IV:3, Folder 6)
  - "The Park Avenue Cubists" (2003), 2002 (Box IV:3, Folder 7)
  - "Mapping Sitting: On Portraiture and Photography", 2002 (Box IV:3, Folder 8)
  - "Diane Arbus: Family Albums" (2004), 2003 (Box IV:3, Folder 9)
  - "Paul Kos", 2003 (Box IV:3, Folder 10)
  - "Erro", 2004 (Box IV:3, Folder 11)
  - "Modern American Painting from the NYU Art Collection", 2004 (Box IV:3, Folder 12)
  - "Ok/Okay", 2005 (Box IV:3, Folder 13)
  - "Paper Museums", 2005 (Box IV:3, Folder 14)
  - "The Downtown Book: The New York Art Scene 1974-1984", 2006 (Box IV:3, Folder 15)
  - "Lee Mullican: An Abundant Harvest of the Sun" (2006), 2005 (Box IV:3, Folder 16)
  - "Beyond the White Cube" (2007), 2006 (Box IV:3, Folder 17)
  - "Semina Culture" (2007) (Box IV:3, Folder 18)
  - "The Poetics of Cloth", 2008 (Box IV:3, Folder 19)
  - "New York Cool", 2008 (Box IV:4, Folder 1)
  - "John Wood: On the Edge of Clear Meaning" (2009), 2008 (Box IV:4, Folder 2)
  - "Damaged Romanticism" (2009), 2008 (Box IV:4, Folder 3)
  - "Artur Carter: Sculptures, Paintings, Drawings", 2009 (Box IV:4, Folder 4)
  - "Arthur Carter Sculpture and Drawings", 2009 (Box IV:4, Folder 5)
  - "John Storrs" (2011), 2010 (Box IV:4, Folder 6)
  - "Concrete Improvisations: Collages and Sculpture", 2011 (Box IV:4, Folder 7)
  - "Fluxus", 2011 (Box IV:4, Folder 8)
  - "Storied Past" Four Centuries of French Drawings from the Blanton Museum of Art", 2011 (Box IV:4, Folder 9)
  - "Sonia Delaunay", 1980 (Box IV:5)
  - "Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted", 1980 (Box IV:5)
  - "Contemporary Indian Art", 1985 (Box IV:5)
  - "Dreaming: The Gokstadt" (1990), 1985 (Box IV:5)
  - "The Lagoon Cycle" (1987), 1985 (Box IV:5)
  - "Morality Tales: History Painting in the 1980s", 1987 (Box IV:6)
  - "Awards in the Visual Arts 6", 1987 (Box IV:6)
  - "Success Is A Job In New York", 1989 (Box IV:6)
  - "Peter Hujar", 1990 (Box IV:6)
  - "Interrogating Identity", 1991 (Box IV:6)
  - "Anyone in New York", 1993 (Box IV:6)
  - "Suspension of the Law: Rene Santos, A Retrospective", 1994 (Box IV:6)
  - "Kazia", 1995 (Box IV:7)
  - "Nahum B. Zenil: Witness to the Self" (1997), 1996 (Box IV:7)
  - "Priceless Children: American Photographs 1890-1925" (2002), 2001 (Box IV:8)
  - "Seeing and Believing: The Art of Nancy Burson", 2002 (Box IV:8)
  - "Electrifying Art: Atsuko Tanaka 1954-1968", 2004 (Box IV:8)
  - "Moving Pictures: American Art and Early Film 1880-1910", 2005 (Box IV:8)
  - "The Geometry of Hope", 2007 (Box IV:9)
  - "Richard Diebenkorn in New Mexico", 2007 (Box IV:9)
  - "Kunstlerplakate der DDR 1967-1990", 2009 (Box IV:10)
  - "Icons of the Desert: Early Aboriginal Paintings from Papunya", 2009 (Box IV:10)
  - "Soto: Paris and Beyond 1950-1970", 2012 (Box IV:10)
  - "Ernest Cole, Photographer", 2010 (Box IV:11)
  - "Alice Aycock Drawings: Some Stories are Worth Repeating", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - "Beat Memories: Photographs of Allen Ginsberg", 2010 (Box IV:11)
  - "Energy that is All Around: Mission School: Chris Johanson, Margaret Kilgallen, etc", 2014 (Box IV:11)
  - "Energy that is All Around: Happening at In Your Mind", limited edition catalog (179/250), undated (Box IV:11)
  - "Radical Presence: Black Performance in Contemporary Art", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - "Toxic Beauty: The Art of Frank Moore", 2012 (Box IV:11)
  - "An Opening of the Field: Jess, Robert Duncan, and their Circle", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - Leslie-Lohman's Art After Stonewall, 1969-1989 Special Edition of The Archive and Lapel Pins, 2019 (Box Shared University Archives 055, Folder 2)
  - "NeoRealismo: The New Image in Italy, 1932-1960", 2018 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "The Expressionist: Fritz Ascher", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Metamorphoses: Ovid According to Wally Reinhardt", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Art After Stonewall, 1969-1989", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - "Modernisms: Iranian, Turkish, and Indian Highlights from NYU's Abby Weed Grey Collection", 2019 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - "Taking Shape: Abstraction from the Arab World, 1950s-1980s", 2020 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Anne Brigman: A Visionary in Modern Photography", 2020 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Series V: Photographs, 1964-1984; 10 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains photographic materials largely of and related to exhibitions hosted at the Grey Art Gallery.
  - The New York Painter, undated (Box V:1, Folder 1)
  - The New York Painter, undated (Box V:1, Folder 2)
  - Durand Ruel Exhibition: Photos, opening at Wildenstein, undated (Box V:1, Folder 3)
  - Durand Ruel Exhibition: Photos/Wildenstein Benefit. (Stephanie Rancou), undated (Box V:1, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Photos: Concrete Expressionism, undated (Box V:1, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition: Bernard Childs, 1964 April 14-May 15 (Box V:1, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions -- Recent Acquisitions, 1966 (Box V:1, Folder 7)
  - University of Connecticut Exhibition Installation Photographs, 1973 (Box V:1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, undated (Box V:1, Folder 9)
  - Hudson River Museum Show Installation Photos, 1971 October 2-November 11 (Box V:2, Folder 1)
  - Loeb Show Photos, 1973 June-August (Box V:2, Folder 2)
  - Notre Dame Installation Photos, 1973 January 14-February 25 (Box V:2, Folder 3)
  - Irish Directions of the 70s Photographs, 1975 (Box V:2, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Photographs, undated (Box V:2, Folder 5)
  - Gallery of Living Art Revisited Philadelphia Museum Corr., undated (Box V:2, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Photographs, undated (Box V:2, Folder 7)
  - Selections from the NYU Collection, 1968 April 27-May 4 (Box V:2, Folder 8)
  - Abby Grey's Honorary Dinner, undated (Box V:2, Folder 9)
  - Circa 1776 / Salute Press Photos, undated (Box V:2, Folder 10)
  - Hudson River Museum Exhibition Benefit Reception (1 of 2), 1971 October 3 (Box V:2, Folder 11)
  - Hudson River Museum Exhibition Benefit Reception (2 of 2), 1971 October 3 (Box V:3, Folder 1)
  - NYU Art Exhibition Benefit, 1967 (Box V:3, Folder 2)
  - Report from SoHo Photographs, undated (Box V:3, Folder 3)
  - Recent American Etching Photographs, undated (Box V:3, Folder 4)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (1 of 3), undated (Box V:4, Folder 1)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (2 of 3), undated (Box V:4, Folder 2)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (3 of 3), undated (Box V:4, Folder 3)
  - Beatrix Potter -- National Trust Correspondence, 1977 (Box V:4, Folder 4)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy Essays by Christopher Scott, undated (Box V:4, Folder 5)
  - Parviz Tanavoli/Locks from Iran -- Clipping File, undated (Box V:4, Folder 6)
  - Marjorie Strider Big Box PR, undated (Box V:4, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Poster Exhibition PR, undated (Box V:4, Folder 8)
  - Aspects of American Realism Clippings, undated (Box V:4, Folder 9)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Press Photos and Negatives, undated (Box V:4, Folder 10)
  - Sandman -- Black and White Photos, undated (Box V:4, Folder 11)
  - Restricted Series II: Development: Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z, undated (Box V:4, Folder 12)
  - Restricted Series II: Development: Panoramic Photography Lenders L- (2 of 2), undated (Box V:4, Folder 13)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (1 of 3), undated (Box V:5, Folder 1)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (2 of 3), undated (Box V:5, Folder 2)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (3 of 3), undated (Box V:5, Folder 3)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Hunt Institute and Other Miscellaneous Photos, undated (Box V:5, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Balet/Palmer/Smyth Press Photos, undated (Box V:5, Folder 5)
  - House of Iran Exhibit, undated (Box V:5, Folder 6)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Documents/Objects -- Wright Rugs, undated (Box V:5, Folder 7)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Photographs, undated (Box V:5, Folder 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Press Photographs, undated (Box V:5, Folder 9)
  - Wilmarth Black/White Photos, undated (Box V:5, Folder 10)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Press Photos/Negatives, undated (Box V:5, Folder 11)
  - Panoramic Photography, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Assorted Audubon Reprints, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Series I: Bill Komosky, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 4)
  - Around the Square -- Old Photographs, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Around the Square -- M. Feldstein Press Photos, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Edward Henderson, 1981-1982 (Box V: 6, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Tiffany Bulletin, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Tiffany Photos, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 9)
  - Tiffany Color Transparencies, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Hare/Kiesler Press Photos, undated (Box V: 6, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Audubon Photographs, undated (Box V: 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Series I: Audubon Negatives (1 of 2), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Audubon Negatives (2 of 2), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Winokur (Press Only), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Steve Steigman (Press Only), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Bruce Weber (Press Only), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Cosimo di Leo Ricatto (Press Only), undated (Box V: 7, Folder 8)